file-extensions.org 2017-07-12

# Privacy policy

## File-Extensions.org privacy policy:

File-Extensions.org respects your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us on our web site. To that end, unless you designate otherwise or we state otherwise in this policy or at the time information is collected, any personal information you provide to File-Extensions.org will be known only to two parties: you and File-Extensions.org. 

To put it simply, we use your information only to provide a better service and make the site more useful.   
At this time no user personal information are used or displayed at our website.

##  **Impersonal tracking information** and advertising

Impersonal tracking information (such time spent on site or on a specific page or which article gets the most hits) is used in aggregate form for product development purposes and to generally inform advertisers about the nature of our subscriber base.

Information collected passively with used some internet technologies like Internet Protocol address, cookies, Internet Tags etc. These informations help us adapt page content to our users and helps to our advertisers and sponsors better understand our visitors

On our website are showed adverts from 3rd advertisement companies. These companies can use informations (but not name, address, email and phone numbers) about your visits ours and other pages to provide advertisement for good and services you are interested about.

Google Inc., as supplier 3rd companies, use for showing advertisement cookies on our pages. With the cookie file DART can Google Inc. shows advertisement to users based on their visites on our pages and other internet pages.

Users can read [Privacy Policy for Google Ads and the Google content network](http://www.google.com/privacy_cookies.html) and [sign off](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/opt-out.html) from using DART cookies files.

Most of internet browsers are automatickly setup to accept cookie files, but you can setup your browser to don't accept cookies or notice every time when page is trying send them to you. When cookies are not allowed some function and Google services should't work properly.

If you want you can every time [refuse cookie files from Google Inc.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) in Google content network through [Refuse cookie files from DoubleClick](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx).

Advertising Cookie Opt-out Plugin permanently disable in internet browsers Firefox and Internet Explorer saving "DoubleClick cookie", used by Google for visit rate evaluation used for advertising purposes.

In some cases, we use geo-targeted advertising or section-placed advertising so advertisers can reach the users for whom their products are the most pertinent. This is to improve effectiveness and appreciation of ad messages. We disclose advertising viewership information to advertisers only in aggregate form.

## Other sites

File-Extensions.org website contains many links to other sites on the Web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other Web sites. 

## Who can I ask if I have additional questions

If you have any further questions or concerns about our privacy policy and use of personal information, please send them to privacy!!remove-this-text!! at file-extensions.org.
